http://www.southfloridafun.com/terms-of-use-policies

Terms of Use & Policies - GFLGLCC - Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, FL
Join Our Email List
For Email Marketing you can trust.
Website Terms of Use
Members and guests of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce are encouraged to familiarize themselves with our Website Terms of Use, and Privacy & Photo Policy. Details are on this page.
Below is a description of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce website terms of use. Your use of this Site indicates your agreement to be bound by these Terms and Conditions as in effect from time to time. If you do not agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions, promptly exit this Site. If you have any questions or concerns about these terms of use as they apply to the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce website, please do not hesitate to contact us via telephone at 954-523-3500 or by email at Keith@gflglcc.org.
Introduction
The terms and conditions of use of this Site are governed solely by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce of Commerce. (Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce). This page sets out the terms and conditions ('Terms and Conditions') which will govern your use of the Site and compliance with these rules is a condition to your use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify these Terms and Conditions. Accordingly, please review this page often. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce will give notice of changes to the Terms and Conditions by posting the revised Terms and Conditions on this Site, together with the date the Terms and Conditions were last updated. Modifications will be effective immediately upon posting.
Indemnity
You agree to indemnify and hold the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce and its subsidiaries, affiliates, officers, agents, employees, partners and licensors harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to or arising out of Content you submit, post, transmit or otherwise make available through this site, your use of the site, your connection to the site, your violation of the Terms of Use, or your violation of any rights of another.
Ownership and Copyright
All pages within this Site and any material made available for download are the property of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, its subsidiaries, affiliates, vendor and/or licensors. The Site is protected by United States and international copyright and trademark laws. The contents of the Site, including without limitation the text, images, audio, and video, and any materials accessed through or made available for use or download through this site are copyrighted and may not be copied, distributed, modified, reproduced, published or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written consent of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, except that you may download content from the Site to any single computer for your personal use only, provided you keep intact all copyright, trademark, and other proprietary notices and comply with any applicable end user license agreements. No part of any content, form or document may be reproduced in any form or incorporated into any information retrieval system, electronic or mechanical, other than for your personal use (but not for resale or redistribution).
For purposes of these Terms and Conditions, any use of these materials on any other Website is prohibited. You do not acquire ownership rights to any content, document or other materials viewed through the Site. The posting of information or materials on the Site does not constitute a waiver of any right in such information and materials. All software used on this Site is the property of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce or its software suppliers and protected by United States and international copyright laws.
User Information
By using this Site, (1) you represent and agree that you are bound by these Terms and Conditions; and (2) you have read the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's Privacy Policy and consent to the use of your personal information by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce and others in accordance with the terms of and for the purposes set forth in the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's Privacy Policy.
License; Restrictions on Use
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce hereby grants you a nonexclusive license to use the Site solely for your personal use. This license does not include any resale or commercial use of this Site or its contents; any collection and use of any product listings, descriptions, or any prices; any derivative use of this Site or its contents; any downloading or copying of account information for the benefit of another merchant; or any use of data mining, robots, or other data gathering and extraction tools. You may not frame or utilize framing techniques to use, surround or enclose any of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's name, trademarks, service marks, logo, or other proprietary information (including; images, text, page layout, or form) of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce and/or our affiliates or subsidiaries without the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's express written consent. You may not use any meta tags or any other 'hidden text' utilizing the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's name or trademarks without the express written consent of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce.
As a condition of your use of this Website, you warrant to the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce that you will not use the Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these Terms and Conditions. If you breach any of these Terms and Conditions, your authorization to use this Site automatically terminates and you must immediately destroy any downloaded or printed materials. Any rights not expressly granted by these Terms and Conditions or any applicable end user license agreements are reserved by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce.
Trademark Notice
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce of Commerce name and logo are trademarks, owned by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's trademarks may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers or in any manner that disparages or discredits the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce. All other trademarks and logos used in this Site are the trademarks, service marks or logos of their respective owners. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce does not make any claims to the marks of others which might appear on the Site. You gain no right to use any marks of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce or any other entity by virtue of your use of this Site.
Confidential and Proprietary Information/Visitor Submissions
Please refer to our Privacy Policy for an explanation of how we collect, maintain and use confidential and proprietary information from visitors to and users of our Site. By accessing, using or browsing this Site, you acknowledge and understand that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy, do not use this Site. All remarks, suggestions, ideas, graphics, or other information communicated to the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce through its Site (collectively, the 'Submission') will forever be the property of the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce will not be required to treat any Submission as confidential, and will not be liable for any ideas for its business (including without limitation, product or advertising ideas) and will not incur any liability as a result of any similarities that may appear in future Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce products or operations.
Without limitation, the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce will have exclusive ownership of all present and future existing rights to the Submissions of every kind and nature, everywhere. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce will be entitled to use the Submission for any commercial or other purpose whatsoever, without compensation to you or any other person sending the Submission. You acknowledge that you are responsible for whatever material you submit, and you, not the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, have full responsibility for the message, including its legality, reliability, appropriateness, originality, and copyright. You agree not to try to access and not to access any information through the Site which does not pertain to you and which you are not properly authorized to receive. You agree that if you should access information about another individual or entity, or otherwise receive information you are not authorized to receive, or if you become aware that someone else has accessed or attempted to access information that person was not authorized to receive, you will immediately cease such unauthorized access, notify the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce of the unauthorized access, and assist the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce in identifying and correcting the circumstances which permitted such unauthorized access. You will keep confidential all information you receive concerning another individual or entity confidential, shall not use such information, shall return such information to the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce immediately, shall not transmit it to any other person or entity and shall not return it in any electronic or other form.
Minors
This website is intended for use by adults. Persons under age 18 should use this site only with the supervision of a parent or guardian.
Security
You may be required to enter a valid User I.D. and password ('Access Codes') to access certain areas of the Site or to purchase products. It is your sole responsibility to monitor and control use of these Access Codes for all purposes. You accept all responsibility for the security of your Access Codes, and utilization of the Site via the Access Codes. You agree that you shall be solely liable for all authorized and unauthorized access using the Access Codes. Do not disclose your Access Codes to anyone not authorized to act on your behalf. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply.
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, OR THAT DEFECTS IN THE SITE WILL BE CORRECTED. THIS SITE, INCLUDING ANY CONTENT OR INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN IT, AND ANY SITE-RELATED SERVICES, ARE PROVIDED 'AS IS,' WITH ALL FAULTS. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, AND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY SUCH WARRANTIES, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN, OR THE MISUSE OR MISINTERPRETATION OF, ANY INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce DOES NOT WARRANT THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR TIMELINESS OF THE INFORMATION OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITE.
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce DOES NOT WARRANT THAT FILES AVAILABLE FOR DOWNLOAD WILL BE FREE OF VIRUSES, WORMS, TROJAN HORSES OR OTHER DESTRUCTIVE PROGRAMMING. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR IMPLEMENTING PROCEDURES SUFFICIENT TO SATISFY YOUR NEEDS FOR DATA BACK UP AND SECURITY. YOU AGREE THAT the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY COSTS OR DAMAGES ARISING DIRECTLY OF INDIRECTLY FROM ANY SUCH CODE. YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND OF THE INTERNET. YOU ASSUME TOTAL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR YOUR USE OF THIS SITE, ANY SITE-RELATED SERVICES, AND HYPERLINKED WEBSITES. NO ORAL OR WRITTEN INFORMATION OR ADVICE GIVEN BY the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce OR the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce's AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVES SHALL CREATE A WARRANTY OR IN ANY WAY INCREASE THE SCOPE OF THIS WARRANTY. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MAY HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.
Limitation of Liability Regarding Use of Site
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, VENDORS AND/OR LICENSORS AND OTHER THIRD PARTIES MENTIONED ON THIS SITE ARE NEITHER RESPONSIBLE NOR LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE, OR OTHER DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, THOSE RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING IN ANY WAY TO THE SITE, SITE-RELATED SERVICE, CONTENT OR INFORMATION CONTAINED WITHIN THE SITE, AND/OR ANY HYPERLINKED WEBSITE. THIS LIMITATION APPLES (A) WHETHER THE ALLEGED CLAIMS OR DAMAGES ARE BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND (B) REGARDLESS OF WHETHER OR NOT the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. YOUR SOLE REMEDY FOR DISSATISFACTION WITH THE SITE, SITE-RELATED SERVICES, AND/OR HYPERLINKED WEBSITES IS TO STOP USING THE SITE AND/OR THOSE SERVICES. CERTAIN STATE LAWS DO NOT ALLOW LIMITATIONS ON IMPLIED WARRANTIES. IF THESE LAWS APPLY TO YOU, SOME OR ALL OF THE ABOVE DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS, OR LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU, AND YOU MIGHT HAVE ADDITIONAL RIGHTS.
Accuracy and Integrity of Information
Although the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce attempts to ensure the integrity and accurateness of the Site, it makes no guarantees whatsoever as to the correctness or accuracy of the Site. It is possible that the Site could include typographical errors, inaccuracies or other errors, and that unauthorized additions, deletions and alterations could be made to the Site by third parties. In the event that an inaccuracy arises, please inform the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce so that it can be corrected. Information contained on the Site may be changed or updated without notice.
Links or Pointers to Other Sites
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce makes no representations whatsoever about any other Website that you may access through this Site. When you access a non-Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce site, please understand that it is independent from the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, and that the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce has no control over the content on that Website. In addition, a hyperlink to a non-Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce Website does not mean that the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content, or the use, of the linked site. It is up to you to take precautions to ensure that whatever you select for your use or download is free of such items as viruses, worms, Trojan horses, and other items of a destructive nature. If you decide to access any of the third-party sites linked to this Site, you do this entirely at your own risk.
Termination
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to terminate your access to all or part of this Site, with or without cause, and with or without notice.
Statute of Limitations
Any cause of action brought by you against us or our affiliated parties must be instituted within one (1) year after the cause of action arises or be deemed forever waived and barred.
Choice of Law and Venue
This Site is controlled by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce from its offices within the state of Florida, of the United States of America. It can be accessed from all fifty states, as well as from other countries around the world. Each of these places has laws that may differ from those of Florida. By accessing this Site, both you and the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce agree that the statutes and laws of the state of Florida will apply to all matters related to these Terms and Conditions and the use of the Site, without regard to conflicts of laws or principles thereof. Each party also agrees and hereby submits to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the state and federal courts sitting in Broward County, Florida, and waives any jurisdictional, venue or inconvenient forum objections to such courts. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce makes no representation that materials on the Site are appropriate or available for use in other locations and accessing them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.
Severability
In the event that any of the Terms and Conditions are held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, such provisions shall be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that these Terms and Conditions shall otherwise remain in full force and effect.
Entire Agreement
These Terms and Conditions constitute the entire agreement between the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce and you pertaining to the subject matter hereof. In its sole discretion, the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce may from time-to-time revise these Terms and Conditions by updating this posting. You should, therefore, periodically visit this page to review the current Terms and Conditions, so you are aware of any such revisions to which you are bound. Certain provisions of these Terms and Conditions may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices or terms located on particular pages within this Site.
How to Contact the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce of Commerce
If you have any questions or concerns about these Terms and Conditions, then please submit your contact information and remarks in one of the following ways:
Send an email message to Keith@gflglcc.org
Send a written request to
Webmaster
Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce of Commerce
2300 NE 7th Avenue
Wilton Manors, FL 33305
Call us at 954-523-3500
The Webmaster will review your message and respond appropriately.
Thank you.
rev. 2020-06-2
Privacy & Photo Policy
General Statement of Privacy
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce respects the privacy of its members and of those who visit this site. Subject to the provisions of applicable laws, any information you submit to the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce will not be used in any manner to which you have not consented. While the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce does analyze its Website logs to monitor the flow of traffic and make improvements to the site’s content, its Website logs are not personally identifiable, and no attempt to link them to individual visitors to this site is made.
Personally Identifiable Information
We do not collect Personally Identifiable Information about you on the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce Website without your knowledge or action. Your information is collected through the membership registration form, e-mail newsletter registration, and/or event registration forms. This information includes, but is not limited to, your name (first and last), company name, company address, phone number, fax number, e-mail address, and credit card information. You should be aware that if you disclose any information on a bulletin board or in a chat room or other open forum that is hosted by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, others may collect that information to send you unsolicited information from outside the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, or for other purposes.
Use of Personally Identifiable Information
We reserve the option to share your contact information with certain third parties. These can include financial institutions, service providers, contractors, or affiliated organizations. You will always have the ability to opt-out from receiving information from the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce as well as from said third parties.
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes, but is not limited to, information we automatically collect on your use and/or actions on our Website (e.g., user traffic patterns, page views on the Website, click-through rates, search terms that users enter into our search utility). In addition, when a visitor arrives at our site, we collect the IP address, operating system, and browser software used. An IP address (which is not the same as an e-mail address) can tell us the user's internet service provider and, based on that, can suggest the geographic location of the connection. The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce recognizes that certain User Information of a key demographic nature (e.g., race, age, gender, national origin, income), while Non-Personally Identifiable Information, is still of a sensitive nature to users. As a general matter, the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce does not collect such information about you through the LGBTChamber.com Website. However, in recognition of the sensitive nature of such information, in the event the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce comes into possession of such information, whether through your voluntary submission of such information in response to a special feature on the Website or by receiving such information from any of our business partners, such information shall, when coupled with any of your Personally Identifiable Information, itself be deemed to be Personally Identifiable Information and treated by the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce as such.
Use of Non-personally Identifiable Information
As a general matter, Non-Personally Identifiable Information helps us determine how the LGBTChamber.com Website is being used, helps us identify popular areas of the Website, and helps determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities regarding the Website.
Use of “Cookies”
Our Website may use 'cookies' (i.e., a small data file that our Website writes to a user's hard drive) to help track your usage of our site, including what advertising you have seen. Our website cookies do not include personal information about you, but they are unique to each user and include a member ID # (a randomly generated unique number) that enables the LGBTChamber.com Website to identify you when you visit, so you: (1) do not have to remember your username and password each time you visit the Website; and (2) receive any personalized services you requested when you registered.
Neither our Website nor the cookies we write to the hard drives of our users, read any data off of your hard drive outside of our cookies. This includes not reading any cookie files created by other Websites. You can refuse our cookies by turning them off in your browser (for more information on how to do this, please refer to your browser's documentation). You do not need to have cookies turned on in your browser to use our Website; however, without cookies, certain of the automated functions and features of our Website will not be available to you. We also use cookies to measure the click-through rate on e-mails delivered.
Third-Party use of Personal Information
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce Website contains links to other Internet Websites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites, including such sites' use of any information.
Meeting & Event Photo Policy
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce meetings, programs, and events are generally open to all Members and registered guests, including staff and volunteers.
By attending events you acknowledge and agree to grant the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce, organizations affiliated with the Chamber, and authorized representatives the right to record, film, photograph, or capture your likeness in any media now available or hereafter developed and to distribute, broadcast, use, or otherwise disseminate without restriction, in perpetuity, such media without any further approval from you or any payment to you. This grant to the Chamber and its affiliated organizations includes, but is not limited to, the right to edit such media, the right to use the media alone or together with other information, and the right to allow others to use or disseminate the media.
Individuals may request to have photos of themselves removed from Chamber publications by contacting the Chamber office at 954-523-3500. However, the Chamber acknowledges no obligation to comply.
Minors
This website is not intended to collect information about minors. Persons under age 18 should not use this website.
Security
You understand and agree that “perfect” security does not exist anywhere, including on the Internet. When you send credit card information, we encrypt this information between your computer and our server. Other information you send to this site, including email messages, will not be encrypted unless we advise you otherwise. Our Website is protected by a firewall and monitored for security.
Merchant Services
You may be able to access certain information related to third parties at the website, or via links, banner ads or click-throughs from the site, regarding the goods or services of third parties. You understand and agree that your access to or use of those services is a matter entirely between you and the associated third parties, and the Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce shall have no liability whatsoever for any such access or use.
Legal Disclaimer
This site provides information designed to help users cope with their own legal, business, financial, and other needs. This information is not the same as retaining experts in those fields for advice. Although we go to great lengths to ensure the information is accurate, we strongly recommend you consult an expert, including but not limited to a lawyer, accountant, financial services consultant, or other professional as appropriate. Nothing contained in this website is to be considered as the rendering of legal, financial, professional or other advice for specific cases, and users are responsible for obtaining such advice from their own legal, financial or other counsel. The information contained on this site is intended for educational, background and informational purposes only.
Correcting, Updating or Deleting Information
The Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce Website gives users the option to correct, update or delete certain information previously provided to us by the user; however, we will maintain copies of user information to the extent retained as part of our Website's standard backup/archive process. In addition, these procedures will not remove such of your information that has been provided by you to, or collected from you by, the Websites of our business partners. We are not responsible for ensuring the removal or deletion from the Websites of our business partners of your information provided by us to our business partners as permitted by you or otherwise in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
To make changes to your contact information use the Members Only portal at GFLGLCC.org. To opt out of receiving information, please contact us in one of the following ways.
Send an e-mail to Keith@gflglcc.org
Send a written request to
Customer Service/Privacy
Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce
2300 NE 7th Avenue
Wilton Manors, FL 33305
Changes to This Privacy Policy
This privacy policy is available at all times to all users of our Website. Any material changes to this privacy policy will be communicated to users through this Web page. Users are responsible for making use of this resource to stay up to date on the Website Privacy Policy.
rev. 2020-06-2
CONNECT
GFLGLCC - Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce
2300 NE 7th Avenue, Wilton Manors, FL 33305
954. 523.3500
keith@gflglcc.org
© Copyright 2020 GFLGLCC - Greater Fort Lauderdale LGBT Chamber of Commerce. All Rights Reserved. Site provided by GrowthZone - powered by ChamberMaster software.
